<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Jie Huang | International Contact Research Network</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/jie-huang/</link><atom:link href="https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/jie-huang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Jie Huang</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://contact-research-network.github.io/media/icon_hu64ffadcb99b730cc1be4dd985f6074ac_34306_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Jie Huang</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/jie-huang/</link></image><item><title>Postdoctoral Research Position at University of East Anglia</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-5-postdoctoral-research-position-at-university-of-east-anglia/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-5-postdoctoral-research-position-at-university-of-east-anglia/</guid><description>&lt;p>An exciting opportunity has arisen to join a Leverhulme Trust funded project, led by &lt;a href="https://research-portal.uea.ac.uk/en/persons/rose-meleady" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Professor Rose Meleady&lt;/a>, investigating the impact of intergroup contact on prejudice and social cohesion. The goal of the project is to use novel experience sampling methods (ESM) to capture intergroup interactions in real-time and explore their immediate impact on intergroup attitudes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>About the Role:
Faculty of Social Sciences, School of Psychology&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Senior Research Associate
Ref: RA2311&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Salary on appointment will be £38,249 per annum, with an annual increment up to £45,413 per annum.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You will be responsible for designing and programming ESM studies, coordinating data collection, analysing the data using multi-level modelling techniques, and contributing to dissemination and impact activities.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You will have a PhD in a relevant field, experience of independent research, and publications in respected journals within the field. You will have advanced statistical skills and knowledge of intergroup relations research. You will also have strong interpersonal and communication skills, with the ability to work effectively as part of a team.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This full-time post is available from 1 September 2025 on a fixed-term basis for 36 months.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Closing date: 2 June 2025&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://vacancies.uea.ac.uk/vacancies/1514/senior-research-associate-ra2311.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Two Postdoctoral Research Fellow Positions in Social Psychology available at The University of Sydney</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-5-two-postdoctoral-research-fellow-positions-in-social-psychology-available-at-the-university-of-sydney/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-5-two-postdoctoral-research-fellow-positions-in-social-psychology-available-at-the-university-of-sydney/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>One part-time (0.5 FTE) Postdoctoral Research Fellow Position&lt;/strong> available in the School of Psychology, funded by the Australian Research Council (ARC) and led by &lt;a href="https://www.sydney.edu.au/science/about/our-people/academic-staff/fiona-white.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Professor Fiona White&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A 0.5 (FTE) Postdoctoral Research Fellow Position in Social Psychology is available to develop and evaluate a new set of ‘RESPECT against racism e-resources’ for primary school-aged children. The RESPECT e-modules will generate new knowledge about the best-practice content needed to successfully expand school student’s inclusive thinking and racism reduction in both the short- and long-term. It is anticipated that these stand-alone RESPECT e-resources can be used to support teachers’ delivery of a national anti-racism curriculum that is novel, engaging and educational. This position is funded by an Australian Research Council (ARC) project ‘RESPECT Against Racism: Advancing new anti-racist educational e-modules’ (LP240100299) between The University of Sydney, Western Sydney University, University of Technology Sydney and The Cool Australia Trust.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Click &lt;a href="https://usyd.wd105.myworkdayjobs.com/USYD_EXTERNAL_CAREER_SITE/job/Camperdown-Campus/Postdoctoral-Research-Associate-in-Social-Psychology_0133658-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here&lt;/a> for details.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Applications Close: Monday 02 June 2025 11:59 PM&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>One part-time (0.8 FTE) Postdoctoral Research Fellow Position&lt;/strong> available in the School of Psychology, funded by the Australian Research Council (ARC) and led by Professor Fiona White.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A 0.8 (FTE) Postdoctoral Research Fellow Position in Social Psychology is available to develop Mixed-reality (MR) technologies that target the barriers to achieving positive intergroup contact. MR technologies can create highly realistic digital humans, that provide researchers with experimental control, ecological validity, and a unique functionality to change the negative intergroup dynamic via a cooperative exchange, in more natural ways than ever before. It is anticipated that this project will uncover the optimal MR methodologies needed for an immersive, multi-sensorial and dynamic interaction to reduce racism. This position is funded by an Australian Research Council (ARC) project ‘Digital humans as a mixed-reality solution to real-world racism’ (DP250100107) between The University of Sydney and Durham University (UK).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Click &lt;a href="https://usyd.wd105.myworkdayjobs.com/USYD_EXTERNAL_CAREER_SITE/job/Camperdown-Campus/Postdoctoral-Research-Associate-in-Social-Psychology_0133526-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener">here&lt;/a> for details.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Applications Close: Monday 02 June 2025 11:59 PM&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Call for Papers - 35th Meeting of the German Peace Psychology Association, 20-22 June 2025, Bremen (Germany)</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-3-call-for-papers-35th-meeting-of-the-german-peace-psychology-association-2022-june-2025-bremen-germany/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-3-call-for-papers-35th-meeting-of-the-german-peace-psychology-association-2022-june-2025-bremen-germany/</guid><description>&lt;p>We invite conceptual and empirical contributions from all disciplines represented in the broad
field of peace psychology and neighboring disciplines outside psychology, scholars at different
career stages, and others situated in peace psychology more broadly.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Submission Deadline: 22 April 2025&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Location: Constructor University Bremen, Germany&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Travel Stipends: Limited support available for participants from low- and middle-income
countries (contact organizers early).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Organizing Team: Klaus Boehnke, Franziska Deutsch, Monika Liorentaite-Rossdeutscher
(&lt;a href="mailto:pp35@bigsss-bremen.de">pp35@bigsss-bremen.de&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Peace Psychology Conference: &lt;a href="mailto:pp35@bigsss-bremen.de">pp35@bigsss-bremen.de&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://www.dgps.de/uploads/tx_powermail/8zzsbmkls9l1hnav6rtferzxfwb3uz3e.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>