<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Contact Research Network</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/</link><atom:link href="https://contact-research-network.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Contact Research Network</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://contact-research-network.github.io/media/icon_hu64ffadcb99b730cc1be4dd985f6074ac_34306_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Contact Research Network</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/</link></image><item><title/><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/publication/cta/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/publication/cta/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Job opportunity: Assistant Professor in Psychology (Research &amp; Education)</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-assistant-professor-in-psychology-research--education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-assistant-professor-in-psychology-research--education/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Durham Psychology Department got approval to advertise the position of an Assistant Professor in Psychology (Research &amp;amp; Education) open to all areas. The post is advertised as ‘open to all areas’ because we currently do not know the exact number of finally approved posts. The outcome of the current planning round will be announced when student numbers are confirmed in autumn. Ideally, we have new academic staff arriving before the start of next academic year. Depending on additional approval of staff requests later this year, we might revisit the shortlist of the current recruitment. The search panel will consist of members from all three research groups.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To attract many applications from excellent researchers around the globe, please help us to advertise this post widely by using the link below when publicising the vacancy via your networks, societies, and contacts. To help us with the search report, please drop Carolyn a brief email listing your networks and contacts you have used.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Assistant Professor in Psychology (Research &amp;amp; Education) (Job Number: 24000984), Open Date 03/06/2024, Closing Date 01/07/2024.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Presentations from shortlisted candidates are scheduled for Tuesday, 13th August.
Interviews are scheduled for Wednesday, 14th August.
Please hold these dates in your diaries.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://durham.taleo.net/careersection/du_ext/jobdetail.ftl?job=24000984&amp;amp;tz=GMT%2B01%3A00&amp;amp;tzname=Europe%2FLondon" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Job opportunity: post-doc on structural and psychological antecedents of intergroup contact</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-postdoc-on-structural-and-psychological-antecedents-of-intergroup-contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-postdoc-on-structural-and-psychological-antecedents-of-intergroup-contact/</guid><description>&lt;p>An exciting opportunity has arisen for a Postdoctoral Research Associate to join the UEA School of Psychology to conduct studies on the drivers of intergroup contact engagement. In that role, you would work with Rose Meleady, Shelley McKeown-Jones, George Leckie and Belong, the Social Cohesion and Integration Charity. The project aims to identify structural and psychological antecedents of intergroup contact&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This full-time post is available from 1 October 2024 on a fixed-term basis for 36 months. For details, check the job posting.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://vacancies.uea.ac.uk/vacancies/963/postdoctoral-research-associate-ra2223.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>First Network Summit Concluded</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-5-first-network-summit-concluded/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-5-first-network-summit-concluded/</guid><description>&lt;p>🌟 We just completed the inaugural summit of the new international Contact Research Network - thanks to the amazing colleagues who spent the last 2 days with us in London at Birkbeck!🌟&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our conversations highlighted some priorities and opportunities for future research👇
💡Contact interventions can promote understanding in schools (Lindsey) and at work (Libby), and reduce political polarisation (Michèle).
💡Contact in everyday life may also promote understanding, yet we need to further explore how to create successful interactions (Stefania, Deborah &amp;amp; Patrick).
💡There are promising opportunities to use new technologies to promote contact and better intergroup relations - from VR to chatbots (Lukas).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were particularly excited to also hear from early career researchers who will help shape the future of our research field (Jie, Zackary, Diana, Emine and Ditte).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We struck up various new collaborations and can’t wait to see them play out - and to have further contact researchers join us on the journey ahead.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Welcome social</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/publication/publications_link/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/publication/publications_link/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;strong>Join us for a chat and drink after work (after 5pm) on Thursday 29th September to catch up and welcome everyone in the new academic year.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Selection of alcoholic and non-alcoholic drinks provided.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title/><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/admin/config.yml</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/admin/config.yml</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/people/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/people/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>