<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Lukas Wallrich | International Contact Research Network</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/lukas-wallrich/</link><atom:link href="https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/lukas-wallrich/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Lukas Wallrich</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/lukas-wallrich/avatar_hu749f1e944273d7a40659e5e971e33442_32833_270x270_fill_q75_lanczos_center.jpg</url><title>Lukas Wallrich</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/lukas-wallrich/</link></image></channel></rss>s-wallrich/</link></image><item><title>First Network Summit Concluded</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-5-first-network-summit-concluded/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-5-first-network-summit-concluded/</guid><description>&lt;p>🌟 We just completed the &lt;strong>inaugural summit&lt;/strong> of the new &lt;strong>international Contact Research Network&lt;/strong> - thanks to the amazing colleagues who spent the last 2 days with us in London at Birkbeck!🌟&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our conversations highlighted some priorities and opportunities for future research👇
💡Contact interventions can promote understanding in schools (Lindsey), at work (Libby) and in conflict situations (Orkun), and reduce political polarisation (Michèle).
💡Contact in everyday life may also promote understanding, yet we need to further explore how to create successful interactions (Stefania, Deborah &amp;amp; Patrick).
💡There are promising opportunities to use new technologies to promote contact and better intergroup relations - from VR to chatbots (Lukas).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were particularly excited to also hear from early career researchers who will help shape the future of our research field (Jie, Zackary, Diana, Emine and Ditte).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We struck up various new collaborations and can’t wait to see them play out - and to have further contact researchers join us on the journey ahead.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>