<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Patrick Kotzur | International Contact Research Network</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/patrick-kotzur/</link><atom:link href="https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/patrick-kotzur/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Patrick Kotzur</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><image><url>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/patrick-kotzur/avatar_hub1d02f44236ff430bd90877af2daf1e0_238085_270x270_fill_q75_lanczos_center.jpg</url><title>Patrick Kotzur</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/author/patrick-kotzur/</link></image></channel></rss>ck-kotzur/</link></image><item><title>ICRN's monthly colloquia are back!</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-10--icrns-monthly-colloquia-are-back-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2025-10--icrns-monthly-colloquia-are-back-/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are excited to share that we have a new round of wonderful speakers lined up for a brand-new round of the ICRN colloquium! This includes a new section dedicated to the wishes and needs of our early postgraduate researcher community!
While we are busy getting a few last details organised before we release the full list of speakers and schedule, we would like to announce that &lt;em>Prof. Jake Harwood, University of Arizona&lt;/em> will kick us off on &lt;strong>Friday, 31st October 2025, 3-4 pm British time.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>The rhythm is gonna get you: What people do during contact matters&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Jake Harwood, Department of Communication, University of Arizona&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This talk will discuss the importance of considering “what happens” during intergroup contact. It argues that specific activities that parties engage in during contact have implications for the mechanisms likely to mediate contact’s effects. Experimental studies of indirect contact’s effects will be discussed, including studies focusing on musical activity as a particularly potent platform for intergroup contact. The talk concludes with thoughts on the diversity and complexity of “positive intergroup contact.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Please join the talk and add it to your calendar following &lt;a href="https://events.teams.microsoft.com/event/be7b3e09-22a8-4fec-962b-93616d4d2739@7250d88b-4b68-4529-be44-d59a2d8a6f94" target="_blank" rel="noopener">this link&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://events.teams.microsoft.com/event/be7b3e09-22a8-4fec-962b-93616d4d2739@7250d88b-4b68-4529-be44-d59a2d8a6f94" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Job opportunity: Assistant Professor in Psychology (Research &amp; Education)</title><link>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-assistant-professor-in-psychology-research--education/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://contact-research-network.github.io/post/2024-6-job-opportunity-assistant-professor-in-psychology-research--education/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Durham Psychology Department got approval to advertise the position of an &lt;strong>Assistant Professor in Psychology&lt;/strong> (Research &amp;amp; Education) open to all areas. The post is advertised as ‘open to all areas’ because we currently do not know the exact number of finally approved posts. The outcome of the current planning round will be announced when student numbers are confirmed in autumn. Ideally, we have new academic staff arriving before the start of next academic year. Depending on additional approval of staff requests later this year, we might revisit the shortlist of the current recruitment. The search panel will consist of members from all three research groups.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Assistant Professor in Psychology (Research &amp;amp; Education) (Job Number: 24000984), Open Date 03/06/2024, Closing Date 01/07/2024.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Presentations from shortlisted candidates are scheduled for Tuesday, 13th August. Interviews are scheduled for Wednesday, 14th August.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://durham.taleo.net/careersection/du_ext/jobdetail.ftl?job=24000984&amp;amp;tz=GMT%2B01%3A00&amp;amp;tzname=Europe%2FLondon" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Read more&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>